<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on Eric's Blog</title><link>https://blog.erictrang.com/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Eric's Blog</description><image><url>https://blog.erictrang.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url><link>https://blog.erictrang.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 21:34:52 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.erictrang.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UNRAID - Restricting Docker External Access for Self-Hosted Containers and Access via Reverse Proxy</title><link>https://blog.erictrang.com/post/dockerunraidlanonly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 21:34:52 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.erictrang.com/post/dockerunraidlanonly/</guid><description>Note: This doesn&amp;rsquo;t apply to only UNRAID, as it is just Docker configurations but I include steps for UNRAID. I won&amp;rsquo;t be going into creating a reverse proxy (There are plenty of tutorials out there for that but I recommend NGINX Proxy Manager if you are new)
If you self-host a lot of applications you may find that sometimes you worry about what happens if it is compromised. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s an application that holds sensitive information such as a password manager you don&amp;rsquo;t want exposed except in your network (via VPN).</description></item><item><title>Windows &amp; Mac: United at Long Last</title><link>https://blog.erictrang.com/post/windowsmac2in1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 21:34:52 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.erictrang.com/post/windowsmac2in1/</guid><description>Playing GTAV on Windows, while running MacOS. All in one computer.
&amp;hellip;Why? I have an iPhone, Apple Watch, Airpods, and Macbook Pro but sadly no Desktop Mac&amp;hellip; until now. Solutions to docking my Macbook into my monitor using a dongle or eGPU seemed gross. Plus, I saw Linus do it and thought it&amp;rsquo;d be cool 😎
Credits to Linus Tech Tips I also sometimes need to use a Mac. Most recently I used it to jailbreak my iPhone.</description></item><item><title>Configuration for CS:GO, Overwatch, etc</title><link>https://blog.erictrang.com/post/csgosetting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 12:33:52 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.erictrang.com/post/csgosetting/</guid><description>Posting my settings here in case I lose them or want to reference on another machine.
Counter-Strike: Global Offensive (CS:GO) Client Cvars sensitivity 1.25; closeonbuy 1; viewmodel_presetpos 3; cl_autowepswitch 0; net_graph 1; bind mwheelup +jump; bind mwheeldown +jump; apply_crosshair_code CSGO-koN4E-pSyUU-eZ6WC-5PP9a-5WRZQ; Crosshair for reference Overwatch Mouse Mouse: G604 DPI: 1600 Polling rate: 1000</description></item><item><title>Wagyu Mafia 🐄</title><link>https://blog.erictrang.com/post/wagyumafia_2019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 16:42:13 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.erictrang.com/post/wagyumafia_2019/</guid><description> You have probably seen these sandwiches pop up on youtube trending. They&amp;rsquo;re pretty good, straight up sandwiches with wagyu in it.
Bought some of the sauce they call &amp;ldquo;WAGYUSCO&amp;rdquo; but forgot to take pictures of it.
Location</description></item></channel></rss>